<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kishor Jothimurugan</title>
    <link>https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kishor Jothimurugan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/introduction/</guid>
      <description>I am a final year PhD student in Computer Science at the University of Pennsylvania. I am being advised by Rajeev Alur. I received my B.Sc. (Honors) in Mathematics and Computer Science from Chennai Mathematical Institute.
My (broad) areas of interest include formal methods, verification, and machine learning. In particular, I am interested in applying formal methods to improve applicability and reliability of deep reinforcement learning, verifying systems with neural network components, and using machine learning to improve scalability of program analysis and verification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other_projects</title>
      <link>https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/other_projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/other_projects/</guid>
      <description>Other Projects Internships Applied Scientist Internship at Amazon Web Services, AI Labs (Summer 2022). I worked on a project on incorporating execution semantics during training of large language models for code generation. I explored different models for code generation that also predict traces obtained by running the generated code on various inputs. The trace prediction task is added as an auxiliary objective during training in order to improve semantic understanding of code by the model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications * equal contribution, † authors in alphabetical order.
Conference Papers Specification-guided learning of Nash equilibria with high social welfare. Kishor Jothimurugan, Suguman Bansal, Osbert Bastani and Rajeev Alur. International Conference on Computer Aided Verification (CAV), 2022.
[pdf] [arXiv] [code] [slides]
A framework for transforming specifications in reinforcement learning.† Rajeev Alur, Suguman Bansal, Osbert Bastani, Kishor Jothimurugan. Invited Contribution to Henzinger-60, 2022.
[pdf] [arXiv] [slides]
Compositional reinforcement learning from logical specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seas.upenn.edu/~kishor/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
